Up everyone, Tos5 here with a very
special video today. Now, let me just
preface this whole entire video with
something important. I've never actually
watched Wings Club, like not a single
episode in my whole entire life, I don't
even know what a Winkx is. And after
watching episode one of the reboot, I I
still don't. I'm telling you all this
because while I know what I'm reacting
to today is a reboot, even though I
think Winkx Club has already had like
what, nine seasons, 10 movies, and 10
other reboots. I don't know. Well, I
want to make it clear that I'm not going
in with any any biases or any of that
[__] This is all new for me, [__]
So, don't roast my ass if in the
comments if I get any of the names or
like law stuff wrong. I'll I'll be
honest. I don't care if you're a
hardcore Wings Clubber or like a a a a
winker, just know that around here to me
and my audience, Wings Club, it's all
new territory. We're all going in blind
on this one. So, the episode starts with
Bloom on her 16th birthday where she has
randomly got magic fire powers because
she's like a like a fire fairy or some
[__] like her hand catches on fire and
she puts it out by by putting her hand
in a glass of water. Also, she has like
a lot of fairy drawings and [__] around
her room. So, I'm guessing that [__] is
going to come into play later. Like her
dad comes in as like, "Hey [__] I know
how you kids these days." Like, "Oh, so
I got you something special for your
birthday." Okay, so naturally I'm here
thinking, "Oh [__] Bloom's dad just got
like an iPhone 15 or like an iPhone 16."
But but nah, nah, [__] This dude,
this dude in his dirty ass like plaid
green jacket, got her act, he got her
ass a bicycle. He got his six-year-old
daughter a bicycle and thought and
thought it was a big deal. I couldn't
even lie. Like that bike look expensive.
Like I know she was going I know she's
going to be a fairy soon but with wheels
like that she don't need no fairy wings.
She's going like 10 miles per hour with
that [__] So she goes zooming off to
school and when that's when we see two
other fairy [__] or like winces since
the show is called Wings Club. I I still
don't know what a Winkx is. They're
fighting a monster and Bloom's back gets
destroyed and [__] and she gets mad and
and uses a fire palace and the other two
fairies like hey fairy alert that [__]
is a fairy. So, the monster is going to
kill Bloomrad. And okay, just listen cuz
this actually got me pissed off a bit. I
have been bringing up the animation up
to this point, but just keep in mind it
is bad. Like, it is really bad direction
animation wise. It makes me want to [__]
my pants. I couldn't believe it. During
the fight scene, it's it's bright
daylight. Okay. Then suddenly as a fight
is going on, it's night time. Like in a
single frame, it goes from daytime to
night time. What are we even doing here?
Bloom. Bloom just left for school,
didn't she? I thought there was a jump
cut. Like, I thought I was missing five
minutes of the episode, but like I was
watching on the official website, so
that can't be it. Like, dead ass one of
the fairies. I think her name is Stella.
I think she has life powers. I thought,
did she turn off the sun? Did she fall
and accidentally all of the light on
Earth was just gone? Because we do know
these fairy [__] have
interdimensional travel powers. Turning
off the sun doesn't seem like impossible
feat in the world of the Winkx Club. And
what we know based off these first two
minutes. And yes, I I did see say the
first two minutes. Everything I just
said happens within 2 minutes. That's
how fast we're going through this
[__] So Stella and I forgot I forgot
the other name. So I had to look it up.
Her name is Flora. Flora is the fairy of
nature. Stella is the fairy of life. But
they can both open portals for some
reason, which I would think only a fairy
of space or portals could do that. But
okay, here we go. Like, I guess we're
doing this then. Still and Flora open up
a portal to somewhere. They don't really
say. The portal appears in the sky and
[__] and they fly into it and we just
kind of cut to the next day. Well,
Fuentilla told Bloom she's a fairy, I
guess, off stream and she just should
just go to school with them. at uh I
think the world of fairies. It It's
called Alfa. Like so they just use the
fairy magic wings club palace to open a
portal and her parents just let her go
with these two strangers. I I don't
think her parents know they're fairies
at this point. So to them it looks like
she's living with two prostitutes which
I I think would be even more worrisome
than if if if she went with fairies like
if you get what I mean. And oh my god
[__] This is where we learned
everybody in the world is a fairy. I I
always thought it was like Sailor Moon
where like characters transform and save
the day and they have secret identities,
but no, there are million millions of
these fairy [__] Still and fairy and
and Flora the fairy [__] Both of them
are fairies. They take Boom to the dorm
room where we meet all the other
characters.
Musa, fairy of music. Love that beat.
She's really good. But I'll be honest, I
struggle to remember the names where
what all the other characters are cuz
the internet they went by so fast. If
you haven't noticed yet, we speedrun
this [__] Like on God, I I I don't mean
just me like I I'm speeding through the
episode. Like I mean all of us like
you're included. We're all being pulled
at last speed against our will in this
[__] when all we want to do is learn
about the characters. Like even little
things that don't matter like their
names. I guess we'll learn more about
everybody in the future episodes cuz
that's all we get to see of them. It's
like 40 45 seconds. So Bloom goes to
meet the I don't know leaders of the
campus. I I I I'm saying professors. I
don't know if that's what they are, but
that that's what I'm using. And it's an
old fairy and an old witch. And we learn
witches and fairies are going to school
together. And not everybody likes that
because witches are are evil and fairies
are good. But they can both use the same
kind of magic. I I don't really know the
difference between fairy magic and witch
magic. They still didn't say. Speaking
of witches, there's like this this group
of three bad [__]
or or witches, and I don't remember
their names. I I know the main one is
Aie cuz she uses a magic and [__] like
ice magic. And one of them can use storm
magic. So, I'm guessing her name is
Stormy. Stormy or some
Oh. Oh. Oh, I was I was I was right. Her
name is Stormy. What What's the other
one's name? Dy like do dark magic. Why
not doy? That's a stupid name. But I I
like these witches. Bloom floor and
Stella get in trouble for I think they
were blamed for the monster going to
earth and breaking [__] even though it
wasn't really their fault. And they were
ordered to clean the statues in front of
the school. The witches see that Bloom
is like a new student which to them also
means easy prey. Of course, I see and
Storm use Stormmy like use the magic and
ice magic witch powers to destroy the
statues and the evil witch professor
sees this. And of course, she gives
Bloom a warning. But it's like [__]
[__]
be be full real right now. Do you not
see the statue is covered in ice and
electricity particles? Do do they not
have cameras in the fairy world of Alfa?
Bloom. Bloom can use fire magic. How? H
how the [__] How the [__] do you think
she knocked over the statue? Are you Are
you Are you stupid? Are you stupid? You
are supposed to be the leader of this
camp is like, "Are you stupid?" So for
ex
at at the magical animal bound place and
then Riku from Kingdom Hearts Noah, but
he has like red hair. I I can only
assume he's going to be Bloom's evil
twin brother because they have the same
hair and eye color. And Bloom says
something about recognizing him, but I
don't know. And to tell you the truth, I
don't care. Bloom feels bad when she
sees the animals on the farm when calls.
So the evil witch [__] gives her a
remote as like, "Set them free, [__]
Do do it." So Bloom does and RKU gets
all mad like, "No, what are you doing?"
That was supposed to keep them in a do
state and [__] You ruin everything.
So the animals all go berserk, right?
And break out. And you know what? This
seems like a job for the specialist. So,
a group of hot anime bros shows up, but
they're really not that hot. Like, in in
in the reboot, their designs are
actually ugly as [__] Sky lost all the
appeal he had from the original Wings
Club, which actually reminded me a lot
of of Bottleby from Sock Underground. If
you know, you know. Like, it's insane
how much these new designs are a
downgrade and [__] But anyways, they're
called the specialist because because I
don't know why they still didn't tell us
what a specialist is, but they got
shields and and whips. That's it. And
they actually suck a whole lot. Like the
fairies have to come in and help them.
So, I don't really know why they're
called specialists when they can't get
the [__] done when the time calls for.
They get most of the animals under
control, though. But the witch [__]
open a portal to earth somehow directly
on top of Bloom's old high school. It's
never explained why all the places on of
all places on Earth when fairies open
their portals, it's always leads to
Northern California. It it it just does.
And yes, Bloom Boom canonically lives in
California. I just looked that up, which
is I don't know why I find that weird.
I'm just like, why is there a fairy in
California? But there is. Bloom runs
into somebody at her school. I I can't
tell if she's a friend or a bully, but
she's kind of a [__] Like, she's not
and I don't mean the [__] She's just
kind of a [__] Like, after bumping
into her, she demands Bloom make a
public apology on social media, but
Bloom says it wouldn't mean anything
since Bloom has no followers on social
media cuz she's like # relatable. So,
the two of them go to the bathroom, but
honestly, I can't remember why. I was
eating a lasagna at the time. It was
either because the monster was chasing
them or the monster went in the bathroom
or because Bloom had to take a massive
dump, but the fairies come in and take
care of the monster and then Bloom goes
back with them to the fairy magic home
world place and the day is saved.
So, after I finished watching episode
one of the reboot, I just had to go back
and see what episode one of the original
show was like. just see what what it was
all about cuz I still have no idea what
Wings Club is. Episode one starts off
pretty much the same as the reboot. But
there's one big thing I noticed
immediately. Is is Bloom supposed to be
poor? Cuz I did not get that from the
reboot. Looking at where she lives, it's
like some actual ghetto [__] Like some
shitty rundown apartment coming to her
house in the reboot where the ceilings
are like 30 feet tall. Look, look at
that [__] They've got like a 30 in flat
screen TV, but but here they got one of
those little box ones. And in the
reboot, the families got these stupid
minimalist paintings all over the place
that they probably spent like 70 bucks
on at the minimum. They even got one of
those chessboards sitting in the middle
of the living room that, you know,
nobody ever uses. Like th this has got
to be some middle to upper class family.
So Ghetto Bloom gets on her back just
like in the reboot. No, she gets her
back just like in the reboot. But in
this version, the back sucks. And Ghetto
Bloom isn't afraid to be a poopy baby
[__] about it either. She takes the
back to school anyway though cuz she
don't she ain't got no other rat. And
just to emphasize how much the living
that get lost out here in these streets.
Her parents talk about how they'll try
better next year to get her a better
gift when she's 17. Like something
that's much more expensive. You can't
make that [__] up. It it took them a
whole goddamn year just to get a back
that cost like four bucks. On the way to
school, Ghetto Bloom runs into her
friend from school that I instantly
recognize from the reboot. And while in
the reboot, I was un sure I wasn't sure
if she was a shitty friend or a bully.
They make it way more clear here where
it's obvious that her name is Mity and
you don't step up on Mity cuz she comes
from a family of wealth. Okay. Like you
know Missy's running like Northern
California cuz the more Bloom sees her,
she turns her ass around. She scadadles.
She She takes a U-turn, she goes uphill.
So I stopped watching at this point cuz
I realized I needed to go take a [__]
cuz I had just finished my lasagna. I
need to get ready to watch episode two
of the reboot before my Betty B time. if
if you want me to go back and review the
original after the wing sub, I I can do
that. Just let me know down below if if
you'd be interested. So So here's what
we're going to do at the end of every
episode cuz there's there's 12 of these
little [__] We're going to be
ranking the individual episodes one
winks out of 10. No, no, I'm not saying
they all get one of 10, but we're
ranking them somewhere between one wink
out of 10 wxes. And then if I said we're
going to come together and rank the
whole damn thing for this one, I'm
thinking of getting a a a solid a solid
two winks out of 10, which isn't good.
It's actually really bad. I'm giving a
two though, only because it could get
worse. But because it hasn't yet, I
think I think even two is a safe bet,
you know? Who knows? Maybe by the end of
the show, Wings will make me [__]
Like, y'all really thought like your
team is you really you really thought we
were going to get a 10 out of 10 out of
you? [__] be crazy. We know someone
was bad. We made suckers. to throw throw
to throw off your garlic. And you know
what? I I hope Wings Club does that. I
hope they I hope they intentionally put
me in a bad spot to be like, "Hey, we're
going to surprise you when you least
expect it." Like, just [__] Like, just
wait until you see episode 11. Anyways,
that thanks for watching watching
[__] And an extra respect, thanks to
all like the fairies who support me over
on Patreon. If you like what I do, maybe
consider supporting me over there. I
don't know. I don't give a [__] Over
[Music]
the edge. Feel like I'm floating through
the air.
The pain I felt is paid for. All is said
and done.
Oh,
I am restricted. Fixed upon the web. I
need to kick the habit that my mind is
breathing in.
Break it. I've got to break it. I've got
spent all my life holding all of it
closely.
I played it in a sense. A feel of
discontent. I'm finally facing it all
fearless.
Feel
it
burning the bridge that keeps us.
I'm here and I'm feeling
fearless.
Exaggerated. That's what you assume.
The story is over now. I must conclude.
I don't watching where I step. Still
hanging in the balance. Not the life I
want to live. I will take it all
standing tall. Feel that way the first
you are.
Oh.
Break out. I've got to see. Break out.
I've got to see. Spend all my life
holding it all closely.
I play it in a field of discontent. I'm
finally facing it all feeling. Feel
it.
Feel it.
[Applause]
[Music]